PERSONAL DETAILS

Name: Muhammad Amirul Rashideen bin Zaidi Phone: +60 13-363 4357

Address: No 32 Jalan Belimbing Besi 5/KU 10 Taman Meru Damai Meru, 41050

Klang

Email: myruldeen@gmail.com



Students in Bachelor in Information Technology with experience and extensive education in software design and application development. Fluent in English with excellent communication and interpersonal skills. A fast learner with strong time management and multi-tasking skills. Strong work ethic in terms of individual settings to drive product success and process efficiency. Strong troubleshooting and problem solving with an analytical mindset

EDUCATION

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia

Jan 2009 - Nov 2013

Sekolah Agama Menengah Tinggi Tengku Ampuan Jemaah – Shah Alam Selangor

Diploma in Information Technology

Aug 2016 - Nov 2019

Universiti Selangor – Bestari Jaya, Selangor

CGPA 3.54

Bachelor in Information Technology

April 2020 - Nov 2022

Universiti Selangor - Bestari Jaya, Selangor

Current CGPA 3.53

HONOR and AWARDS

- Unimaker East Region 4th place winner in Unimaker competition. responsible in JomQ project (Queue Management System).
- Best System Award Participating in University SIDIQ competition (E-complaint management system)
- Final Year Project 1 and 2 Participating in the final year project, web-based system. September 2018 February 2019.
- CHIPTA 2020 participating in the CHIPTA hackathon event by MAMPU. Develop a Garbage Monitoring System

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nano IT Sdn Bhd

IT Technician (Part-time) Plaza Alam Sentral, Shah Alam

Jan 2014 - Apr 2014

• Troubleshoot repair and selling laptop and desktop.

White World Technology Systems

Web Programmer (Part-time) I-SOVO, Shah Alam

Dec 2017 - Jan 2018

• Build and develop POS system, website and inventory management system.

Grab Haulier Sdn Bhd

Backend Software Engineer (Intern) UOA Business Park, Subang Jaya

Aug 2019 - Dec 2019

- Develop, design and maintain pricelist microservices
- Develop, design and maintain web automation.

Freelance project for Final Year Project Full stack mobile development with IOT

Nov 2021 - Apr 2022

- Develop mobile application for Smart Agriculture using IOT.
- Develop, design and testing mobile application, backend and Arduino/esp8266/32 microcontroller.
- Develop and design API for data collection for microcontroller.
- Data visualization and analyze data from microcontroller.

Freelance project for Final Year Project Full stack mobile development with IOT

Nov 2021 - Apr 2022

- Develop mobile application for Solar Monitoring using IOT.
- Develop, design and testing mobile application, backend and Arduino/esp8266/32 microcontroller.
- Develop and design API for data collection for microcontroller.
- Data visualization and analyze data from microcontroller.

SKILLS

- Languages: Malay (proficient) and English (intermediate).
- Programming Skills: JavaScript, C++, PHP, Python
- General Skills: Teamwork, Adaptability, Time Management, Fast Learner
- Study Skills: Computer Fundamental, Programming, Object Oriented Programming
- Other Skills: Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft Office, PowerPoint, Excel

REFERENCES

- Rahayu Handan (Lecturer)
 - +60 139105067
- Ts. Nik Nordiana N Ab Rahman (Lecturer)
 - +60 12-304 3596